<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss xmlns:a10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>News</title><link>https://bengineeri.ng/</link><description>Bengineering</description><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 19:22:38 Z</lastBuildDate><item><guid isPermaLink="false">619bb7cb-c0ed-4b67-a127-8f45ebae46b4</guid><link>https://bengineeri.ng/News/RssLinksAreHere.html</link><category>feedTitle</category><title>Rss Links are Here</title><description>Markerator
 exposes links to the generated Rss in the generated webpages. I'm super excited for this feature, as I've recently given up on ALL news apps and websites, as they're simply just filled with clickbait headlines and AI generated garbage. By using Rss, the user has the ultimate control over what they read and see, and I want websites that make use of Markerator to allow their users the same level of control.
The help text of Markerator is updated to indicate how this feature is now used. I still owe Markerator a healthy does of documentation, but I feel like the help text is a fairly decent way to get started. My next plan for Markerator is to finally allow just more than one &amp;quot;Posts/Blog/News/Projects&amp;quot; page link in the header, and to include Rss generation for each section. I also plan to do some additional code clean up by separating out the Html generation bits. I already did this for Rss and Css, but the code will continue to improve.!
</description><a10:updated>2024-02-28T00:00:00Z</a10:updated></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">aaf9c46d-bab4-48bc-b3d5-29d8a4df5662</guid><link>https://bengineeri.ng/News/RssHasLanded.html</link><category>feedTitle</category><title>Rss Has Landed!</title><description>I think the next big thing I'm going to tackle is adding the ability to generate multiple &amp;quot;posts&amp;quot; pages at the same time. So you could have &amp;quot;Projects,&amp;quot; &amp;quot;News,&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;Journal&amp;quot; all being generated at the same time, each one with it's own Rss feed generation. I also need to link to the Rss file in the actual generated website, but that will come in the future.
Update: There was a bug in the code I pushed that had the &amp;quot;postsTitle&amp;quot; hardcoded to &amp;quot;posts&amp;quot; in the index.html generation, so even though Markerator generated things correctly, it wouldn't link to them correctly.
Update 2: Make that 2 hardcoded bugs ¯_(ツ)_/¯
</description><a10:updated>2024-02-17T00:00:00Z</a10:updated></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1ff62f29-5cac-48de-83d2-46f3162fdaac</guid><link>https://bengineeri.ng/News/2024.html</link><category>feedTitle</category><title>The New Year</title><description>Since early summer, I've been having a number of health issues that have prevented me from doing almost anything other than work, and sleeping. It's been a long bumpy ride, but I believe after many, many visits with my various doctors, we've arrived at a root cause, and have a path forward that won't affect my ability to be productive and spend time with my family.
That being said, I plan on being much more productive this year. My wife is really good at writing down things on paper, and making lists and using calendars, but that's just not now my brain works. I mainly live in Obsidian MD, as I have a terrible memory, and that's the place that I tend to drop all my notes and stream of consciousness ideas. My rough outline for personal projects for the year, in no specific order are:
That's it for me...I'll continue to be here. Hope that 2024 finds you well.
</description><a10:updated>2024-01-02T00:00:00Z</a10:updated></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">793f7be9-bd83-44a4-8497-cf402246fd53</guid><link>https://bengineeri.ng/News/MyBirthday.html</link><category>feedTitle</category><title>Almost my birthday...</title><description>Having finally settled into our new house, despite the mountain of things that still need to be done, I think I'm finally getting into a groove here. My wife and I usually spend one night a week, after we put the kids to bed, having an &amp;quot;alone&amp;quot; night where I get to work on one of my 10 million projects, and she usually works on art or reads a book. Thanks to this, I'm finally getting some forward momentum on Markerator, as well as a game idea that the kids came up with.
I also treated myself to a cheap action cam &amp;quot;GoPro&amp;quot; knock off that I'm really enjoying. I've used it to film timelapses of the sunrise and sunset, timelapses of me driving, and awesome slow motion clips of the hummingbirds at the bird feeder. I have a lot of future plans for this thing, but so far I'm really enjoying it.
43 tomorrow.
</description><a10:updated>2023-08-02T00:00:00Z</a10:updated></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">4e8fe11f-19c1-4d15-93c6-9224e8cc4ae7</guid><link>https://bengineeri.ng/News/Activity.html</link><category>feedTitle</category><title>Activity!</title><description>Late last year/the beginning of this year, my family and I started the process of moving from the city, across states, out to the country. This process turned out to be way more stressful and drawn out than I had expected, so most of my &amp;quot;free time&amp;quot; projects got shoved way, way back on the back burner. However, now that we've moved, and the house is starting to get somewhat organized, I've found some time to work on my personal projects - including this site, and Markerator.
With any luck I'll be updating this site more frequently and will make a habit of it. Fingers crossed.
</description><a10:updated>2023-06-14T00:00:00Z</a10:updated></item><item><guid isPermaLink="false">1c0a50ea-f429-4b72-9015-6f743340790a</guid><link>https://bengineeri.ng/News/Welcome.html</link><category>feedTitle</category><title>Soft launch</title><description>After working a bunch behind the scenes to get my static site generator up to snuff, I am ready to call this the first official version of the Bengineering site. I plan to refactor and add features to Markerator to make it fit for general consumption, but for now it suits my needs fairly well.
As I continue to work on this as well as other projects, I hope to keep the updates to the site flowing. Here's hoping.
</description><a10:updated>2023-01-25T00:00:00Z</a10:updated></item></channel></rss>